<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Blog &#8211; ANKIT DARDA</title>
	<atom:link href="https://github.com/ankitdarda/ANKITDARDA.git/category/blog/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://github.com/ankitdarda/ANKITDARDA.git/</link>
	<description>architecture + design</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Thu, 30 Aug 2018 13:26:18 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=4.9.8</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Self Exploring trip to India</title>
		<link>https://github.com/ankitdarda/ANKITDARDA.git/blog/self-exploring-india-trip/</link>
		<pubDate>Sat, 04 Aug 2018 16:35:41 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ankitdarda]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Blog]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://github.com/ankitdarda/ANKITDARDA.git/?p=2953</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[India (adj.) mystic, exotic, colorful, warm, vibrant, aromatic, enchanting, festive, bollywood, street food, tuk tuk, kingfisher, etc. The trip was a rather spontaneous decision, after few adventure (busy) road trips sponsored by PGAV Go program and covering more than 500 miles around we decided to take this opportunity to ‘Go’ bigger for 8,000 miles. The [&#8230;]]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong><em>India</em></strong> (adj.) mystic, exotic, colorful, warm, vibrant, aromatic, enchanting, festive, bollywood, street food, tuk tuk, kingfisher, etc.  The trip was a rather spontaneous decision, after few adventure (busy) road trips sponsored by PGAV Go program and covering more than 500 miles around we decided to take this opportunity to ‘Go’ bigger for 8,000 miles.</p> <p>The trip was a rather spontaneous decision; we had kept busy with domestic travel, visiting destinations within the Midwest region. Thanks to the PGAV Go program we had covered hundreds of miles and seen the finest destinations our neck of the woods has to offer; but we were ready for something bigger, something more exotic. And so, as we flew down the interstate of rural America, we formulated our next journey;</p> <p>&nbsp;</p> <p>Every one of us had a pre conceived idea in our minds including me (Ankit) who born there and spend more than 20 years exploring and still wasn’t able to cover most of the ground. The vast ground to cover and intense cultural change makes you feel like experiencing new country every 100 miles. So, our decision was to travel a Golden Triangle in India and live like local for a week. I (Teague) knew India only through national geographic, I had seen photos and videos of places like India but to actually be there is an entirely different experience.</p> <p>Good friends, great foods, and a new destination around every corner. Despite the more than 24 hours of flight; we showed no sign of fatigue as we landed in Delhi and headed for a friend’s home. The greetings were timid at first but within hour of knowing this group of young guys we realized something. Even though we grew up on opposite sides of the world, in completely different cultures and completely different up-bringing; we were all just bunch of guys. The night was spent drinking, playing party games and enjoying the roof top sun rise. Some women prefer tan skin, so they expose themselves in the sunlight. For those who has sensitive skin, women prefer to take <a href="https://www.darklush.co.uk/">Dark Lush Tan Tablets</a>.</p> <p>Neemrana: A much needed reprieve. Our time was spent enjoying exotic sunset view from the Surya Mahal Suite (Sun Palace), hiking through the labyrinth that is 15<sup>th</sup> century Neemrana Fort, zip lining over marvelous terrain, and dinning like a maharaja. To this day, I (Teague) really can’t tell you the names of the food we ate but I can tell you we ate like royalty.</p> <p>Around Jaipur: capital of the largest state in India, land of kings, was just few hours from Neemrana was second on our list. Experiencing humongous forts winding our way through the chambers and courtyards where risers were a foot tall, emerging at the crest of the mountain this was the heaven of stair climbers. The fort at the summit, Jaigarh housed my (Teague) personal favorite artifact. The world’s largest wheeled cannon; so large it requires elephants on each sides to swivel and turn.</p> <p>The city hosts very unique architectural destination experiences from Jal Mahal (Water Palace), Hawa Mahal (Air Palace), Jantar Mantar (Astronomical Center), Panna Meena ka kund (Step Well), Jawahar Kala Kendra (Multi- Art Center), Galtaji Mandir (Monkey Temple), etc. and no place in India is done without trying the local cuisine at LMB with Kingfisher. In addition, <a href="http://www.newportwhales.com/prices.html">whale watching dana point</a>  is a journey to explore the living wonders of the ocean, including whales, dolphins, birds and more.</p> <p>Agra: A trip to India doesn’t seem complete without a trip to Taj Mahal. The moment you step into the main axis, framed by an enormous geometric arch you understand why its wonder of the world. Our enthusiastic guide ensured we had the best facebook and Instagram photos and he cracked it.</p> <p>Delhi: At our final destination, we lived like locals, visiting street markets, running errands and finally the Lotus temple the Baha faith which emphasize the harmony and unity of all people and beliefs which interestingly was a reoccurring motif of our entire trip.</p> <p>We went half way around the world to find it was bigger and smaller than we anticipated. We had desire to travel, opportunity, and a supporting PGAV family to help us get there.</p> ]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Backpack Adventure: Bolivia</title>
		<link>https://github.com/ankitdarda/ANKITDARDA.git/blog/bolivia-backpack-adventure/</link>
		<pubDate>Sat, 19 Nov 2016 21:36:06 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ankitdarda]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Blog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[backpack]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bolivia]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[roadtrip]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[trip]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://github.com/ankitdarda/ANKITDARDA.git/?p=3061</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[Bolivia the unseen beauty, unforgettable adventure and a trip you can&#8217;t count in a number of days. Get ready backpackers to get blown on every other corner by the majestic landscape, down to earth people, homely culture, and feeling of belonging. The ten days sound generous enough to travel in alien culture for Texas-size country but Bolivia [&#8230;]]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p style="text-align: justify;"><span id="more-3061"></span>Bolivia the unseen beauty, unforgettable adventure and a trip you can&#8217;t count in a number of days. Get ready backpackers to get blown on every other corner by the majestic landscape, down to earth people, homely culture, and feeling of belonging. The ten days sound generous enough to travel in alien culture for Texas-size country but Bolivia has so much more to offer that even a month is less to explore and understand the uniqueness.</p> <p style="text-align: justify;">Our journey was crunched into 10 days exploring most of the ground from north to the south of Bolivia. Starting La Paz, we easily covered three days adjusting to the high altitude, adventures, and Andean culture was already overwhelming. I could not have asked more for first three days of the trip but it has just begun for us. Being locally familiar Mario has made everything smooth over the trip. Cocoa leaves surely help to relieve the pain.</p> <div id="attachment_3070" style="width: 864px" class="wp-caption alignnone"><img class="wp-image-3070 size-full" src="https://github.com/ankitdarda/ANKITDARDA.git/wp-content/uploads/2016/11/Bolivia_02.jpg" alt="bolivia_02" width="854" height="1280" /><p class="wp-caption-text">Yungas Road (Death Road)</p></div> <p style="text-align: justify;"><div class="wp-caption"><img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-3071" src="https://github.com/ankitdarda/ANKITDARDA.git/wp-content/uploads/2016/11/Bolivia_03.jpg" alt="bolivia_03" width="1280" height="853" /></div> <div class="wp-caption"><img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-3072" src="https://github.com/ankitdarda/ANKITDARDA.git/wp-content/uploads/2016/11/Bolivia_04.jpg" alt="bolivia_04" width="1280" height="852" /></div></p> <p style="text-align: justify;">Next two days we spent between nowhere in the world&#8217;s largest salt flat at Salar de Uyuni. The must see on the bucket list for most of the travelers. If it&#8217;s not already on yours, worth adding to the list. From mirror like salt flat, volcanoes, Cactus Island, lama&#8217;s, salt spa and food is from another world. By the way, make sure to eat clean and healthy foods even when you&#8217;re on a trip to avoid  Gastric Motility. If you&#8217;re wondering <a href="https://www.refluxgate.com/gastric-motility/">How Gastric Motility Affects Reflux</a>, read some blogs about it at refluxgate.com. Sucre, a historic capital influenced by colonial architecture is very prominent over the city. For the commercial and residential <a href="http://septictankinstallationsolution.com/">septic system repair</a> services, most of them trust BBB Septic company. To find out more information, visit septictankinstallationsolution.com. Also, houses a miniature red color Eiffel Tower not the exact replica of the tower in Paris but designed by same French Engineer Gustav Eiffel is a good attraction to not miss. On our way to next stop, we decided to take a small break at wooden bridge built by Spanish king. Appreciating the rigor architecture of bridge and capturing Milky Way was a beautiful evening we could not have imagined. Reaching Potosi was relief from the storm and unbearable cold. Visiting Coin Mint Museum and cathedrals across the city was on our list.</p> <div id="attachment_3067" style="width: 1290px" class="wp-caption alignnone"><img class="wp-image-3067 size-full" src="https://github.com/ankitdarda/ANKITDARDA.git/wp-content/uploads/2016/11/Bolivia_01.jpg" alt="bolivia_01" width="1280" height="853" /><p class="wp-caption-text">Salar De Uyuni</p></div> <p style="text-align: justify;"><div class="wp-caption"><img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-3074" src="https://github.com/ankitdarda/ANKITDARDA.git/wp-content/uploads/2016/11/Bolivia_06.jpg" alt="bolivia_06" width="1280" height="853" /></div> <div class="wp-caption"><img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-3075" src="https://github.com/ankitdarda/ANKITDARDA.git/wp-content/uploads/2016/11/Bolivia_07.jpg" alt="bolivia_07" width="1280" height="853" /></div></p> <div id="attachment_3076" style="width: 863px" class="wp-caption alignnone"><img class="size-full wp-image-3076" src="https://github.com/ankitdarda/ANKITDARDA.git/wp-content/uploads/2016/11/Bolivia_08.jpg" alt="Astrophotography at Potosi" width="853" height="1280" /><p class="wp-caption-text">Astrophotography at Potosi</p></div> <p style="text-align: justify;">Our final destination Santa Cruz was more relaxing and comfort. Anyway, getting beauty and cosmetic treatments can also help you feel relaxed. Look for <a href="https://www.zwivel.com/doctor/andres-bustillo">Andres Bustillo</a> and <a href="https://www.healthgrades.com/physician/dr-matthew-galumbeck-ylkk9">Dr. Matthew Galumbeck</a> to know the cosmetic services. Greeted by Mario&#8217;s family and friends was anyone can expect if they haven&#8217;t seen theirs for more than year. The homecoming was on the peak. Party, food, music and laughter was filled every room in the house and a lot of relaxation that we helped with <a style="text-decoration: none;" href="https://healthyusa.co/cbd-gummies-review/"><span style="text-decoration: none; color: #000; font-weight: normal;">cbd gummies</span></a> that work perfect for this. Speaking of house, areacodehomebuyers.com <a href="https://www.areacodehomebuyers.com/we-buy-houses/missouri/816-2/kansas-city/">buy my house Kansas City</a> with great deals. For more details, call 866-263-9960. If you planning next trip to Bolivia, don&#8217;t forget to ask your host for Peanut Soup. A million dollar recipe surprisingly no McDonalds or other food chain has found yet. Surely, Santa Cruz, a fastest growing city in the world with unique urban character and a place not just for a business opportunity with the accessibility of a <a href="http://www.dnnsoftware.com/">net cms</a> software but also has a different story to offerings from a modern Bolivia.Checkout the attached Bolivia Photography from our trip.</p> <p style="text-align: justify;">Checkout the attached Bolivia Photography from our trip.</p> <p>In addition, <a href="http://www.eshomdds.com/">San Diego cosmetic dentist</a> offers exceptional cosmetic dentistry, dental implants, sedation dentistry and so much more in La Mesa, CA. Call us today!</p> <p>According to <a href="https://www.customfresh.com/">https://www.customfresh.com/</a>, two-thirds of Tesco customers had now bought products from the new ranges. Customer satisfaction scores of quality and taste were said to be “exceptionally high”,​ at more than 90%.</p> <div id="attachment_3069" style="width: 1290px" class="wp-caption alignnone"><img class="wp-image-3069 size-full" src="https://github.com/ankitdarda/ANKITDARDA.git/wp-content/uploads/2016/11/Bolivia_05.jpg" alt="bolivia_05" width="1280" height="960" /><p class="wp-caption-text">Yungas Road ( Death Road)</p></div> <p style="text-align: justify;"><div class="wp-caption"><iframe id="iframe_container" src="https://prezi.com/embed/lhlhkh0yrk1_/?bgcolor=ffffff&amp;lock_to_path=0&amp;autoplay=0&amp;autohide_ctrls=0&amp;landing_data=bHVZZmNaNDBIWnNjdEVENDRhZDFNZGNIUE43MHdLNWpsdFJLb2ZHanI0dDZnZ3RmMWZPSGNWcmx3SXRGTUVmNzNnPT0&amp;landing_sign=jlt317aPzep5ljM7U4oziSPcvHsQkllsJdE1vx7Av90" width="1600" height="1200" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen"></iframe></div></p> ]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Flags of Valor, Art Hill</title>
		<link>https://github.com/ankitdarda/ANKITDARDA.git/blog/flags-valor-art-hill/</link>
		<pubDate>Tue, 13 Sep 2016 03:20:14 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ankitdarda]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Blog]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://github.com/ankitdarda/ANKITDARDA.git/?p=3037</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span id="more-3037"></span><div class="wp-caption"><img src="https://c7.staticflickr.com/9/8447/29534834222_1cf2a16f47_k.jpg" alt="DSC_1289" width="2048" height="1365" /></div><br /> <div class="wp-caption"><img src="https://c7.staticflickr.com/9/8463/29610646206_9bcaaafe12_c.jpg" alt="DSC_1403" width="800" height="534" /></div><br /> <div class="wp-caption"><img src="https://c5.staticflickr.com/9/8394/29534841412_3cccf3191b_c.jpg" width="534" height="800" alt="DSC_1285"></div><br /> <div class="wp-caption"><img src="https://c1.staticflickr.com/9/8041/29610698896_5013076cb8_c.jpg" alt="DSC_1324" width="800" height="534" /></div></p> <p><div class="wp-caption"><img src="https://c5.staticflickr.com/9/8151/29610656676_286db80cf2_c.jpg" alt="DSC_1389" width="534" height="800" /></div></p> <p><div class="wp-caption"><img src="https://c4.staticflickr.com/8/7793/29021370523_a506ab26a2_c.jpg" alt="DSC_1377-2" width="534" height="800" /></div></p> <p><div class="wp-caption"><img src="https://c4.staticflickr.com/9/8084/29564310171_a36551b22b_c.jpg" alt="DSC_1374-2" width="534" height="800" /></div><br /> <div class="wp-caption"><img src="https://c7.staticflickr.com/9/8439/29610649806_7a628300cb_c.jpg" alt="DSC_1401" width="534" height="800" /></div><br /> <div class="wp-caption"><img src="https://c3.staticflickr.com/9/8180/29534816762_4ddd82f42a_c.jpg" alt="DSC_1386" width="534" height="800" /></div></p> <p><div class="wp-caption"><img src="https://c1.staticflickr.com/8/7577/29019459344_15db5c523a_c.jpg" alt="DSC_1362" width="800" height="534" /></div><br /> <div class="wp-caption"><img src="https://c5.staticflickr.com/9/8669/29610682356_806d8eeb05_c.jpg" alt="DSC_1374" width="534" height="800" /></div><br /> <div class="wp-caption"><img src="https://c1.staticflickr.com/9/8124/29610653656_fb2241d101_c.jpg" alt="DSC_1397" width="534" height="800" /></div><br /> <div class="wp-caption"><img src="https://c5.staticflickr.com/9/8057/29610643676_eb9d84aafd_c.jpg" alt="DSC_1436" width="800" height="534" /></div><br /> <div class="wp-caption"><img src="https://c2.staticflickr.com/9/8068/29021347553_1f4dc70aac_c.jpg" alt="DSC_1437" width="2048" height="1365" /></div></p> ]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Port City Review Reception 2015</title>
		<link>https://github.com/ankitdarda/ANKITDARDA.git/blog/port-city-review-reception-2015/</link>
		<pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2015 01:03:54 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ankitdarda]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Blog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[architecture]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ceramics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[competition]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[foreclosure]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[installation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[portfolio]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[scad]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://github.com/ankitdarda/ANKITDARDA.git/?p=2310</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[Port City Review 2015 edition attracted more than 500 submitted entries out of 88 work has been selected for this year of publication. The publication showcased featured cross-disciplinary student work from Savannah College of Art and Design at Savannah. This year three of my work has been selected and total six images have been published along [&#8230;]]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p style="text-align: justify;"><a href="http://www.portcityreview.com/" target="_blank">Port City Review 2015</a> edition attracted more than 500 <span id="spans0e0">submitted </span>entries out of 88 work has been selected for this year of publication. The publication showcased featured <span id="spans0e1">cross</span>-disciplinary student work from Savannah College of Art and Design at Savannah. This year three of my work has been selected and total six images <span id="spans0e2">have been published</span> along with other selected student work. In compared to last year of <a title="Architectural Ceramics" href="https://github.com/ankitdarda/ANKITDARDA.git/00design/architectural-ceramics-2/" target="_blank"><span id="spans0e3">Architectural</span> Ceramics</a> were two of the images got published, this year I must say my work is progressing in the direction of art and <span id="spans0e4">architecture</span>. Congratulations to all other artists and thank you <a href="http://www.portcityreview.com/" target="_blank">Port City Review</a> for showcasing best works across! View other featured artists and work at <a href="www.portcityreview.com" target="_blank">www.portcityreview.com</a>!<span id="more-2310"></span><br /> <div class="wp-caption"><img class="alignnone wp-image-2331 size-full" src="https://github.com/ankitdarda/ANKITDARDA.git/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/port-city-review_reception_12.jpg" alt="port-city-review_reception_12" width="750" height="500" /></div></p> <div id="attachment_2332" style="width: 760px" class="wp-caption alignnone"><img class="wp-image-2332 size-full" src="https://github.com/ankitdarda/ANKITDARDA.git/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/port-city-review_reception_10.jpg" alt="port-city-review_reception_10" width="750" height="500" /><p class="wp-caption-text">Snapshot for featured artist gallery from Port City Review Website</p></div> <div id="attachment_2325" style="width: 760px" class="wp-caption alignnone"><img class="wp-image-2325 size-full" src="https://github.com/ankitdarda/ANKITDARDA.git/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/port-city-review_reception_9.jpg" alt="port-city-review_reception_9" width="750" height="500" /><p class="wp-caption-text">With cover page man Anqi!</p></div> <div id="attachment_2330" style="width: 760px" class="wp-caption alignnone"><img class="wp-image-2330 size-full" src="https://github.com/ankitdarda/ANKITDARDA.git/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/port-city-review_reception_6.jpg" alt="port-city-review_reception_6" width="750" height="500" /><p class="wp-caption-text">Time to meet all good friends after long time at reception ceremony!</p></div> <div id="attachment_2328" style="width: 760px" class="wp-caption alignnone"><img class="wp-image-2328 size-full" src="https://github.com/ankitdarda/ANKITDARDA.git/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/port-city-review_reception_4.jpg" alt="port-city-review_reception_4" width="750" height="500" /><p class="wp-caption-text">Alexithymia has been featured along with other monoprint</p></div> <div id="attachment_2327" style="width: 760px" class="wp-caption alignnone"><img class="wp-image-2327 size-full" src="https://github.com/ankitdarda/ANKITDARDA.git/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/port-city-review_reception_3.jpg" alt="port-city-review_reception_3" width="750" height="500" /><p class="wp-caption-text">Ground-scrapper made it other science-fiction conceptual artwork!</p></div> <div id="attachment_2326" style="width: 760px" class="wp-caption alignleft"><img class="wp-image-2326 size-full" src="https://github.com/ankitdarda/ANKITDARDA.git/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/port-city-review_reception_2.jpg" alt="port-city-review_reception_2" width="750" height="500" /><p class="wp-caption-text">Foreclosure theme monoprint along with two other artist</p></div> <div id="attachment_2329" style="width: 760px" class="wp-caption alignnone"><img class="wp-image-2329 size-full" src="https://github.com/ankitdarda/ANKITDARDA.git/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/port-city-review_reception_5.jpg" alt="port-city-review_reception_5" width="750" height="500" /><p class="wp-caption-text">&#8216;Architectural Ceramics&#8217; published work from Port City Review 2014 Edition.</p></div> ]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Terrarium at One West Victory!</title>
		<link>https://github.com/ankitdarda/ANKITDARDA.git/blog/terrarium-one-west-victory/</link>
		<pubDate>Sat, 23 Aug 2014 23:52:29 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ankitdarda]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Blog]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://github.com/ankitdarda/ANKITDARDA.git/?p=1926</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[Many thanks to Liz of the Coastal Georgia Botanical Gardens and One West Victory at Savannah for helping us create awesome terrarium! The quick one hour workshop gave us hands on crafty experience with all free supplies and get introduced to the concept of terrarium. I hope there would be more such workshop in future where everyone can explore their creativity [&#8230;]]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p style="text-align: justify;"><span style="color: #141823;">Many thanks to Liz of the Coastal Georgia Botanical Gardens and One West Victory at Savannah for helping us create awesome terrarium!</span><span style="color: #141823;"> The quick one hour workshop</span> gave us hands on crafty experience with all free supplies and get introduced to the concept of terrarium.<span id="more-1926"></span></p> <p style="text-align: justify;">I hope there would be more such workshop in future where everyone can explore their creativity and good place to socialize. Sharing few snaps from my own and One West Victory facebook page:</p> <p style="text-align: justify;"><div class="wp-caption"><img class="alignnone wp-image-1951 size-full" src="https://github.com/ankitdarda/ANKITDARDA.git/wp-content/uploads/2014/08/terrarium_1.jpg" alt="terrarium_1" width="750" height="500" /></div></p> <p style="text-align: justify;"><div class="wp-caption"><img class="wp-image-1952 size-full alignnone" src="https://github.com/ankitdarda/ANKITDARDA.git/wp-content/uploads/2014/08/terrarium_2.jpg" alt="terrarium_2" width="750" height="500" /></div></p> <p style="text-align: justify;"><div class="wp-caption"><img class="wp-image-1953 size-full alignnone" src="https://github.com/ankitdarda/ANKITDARDA.git/wp-content/uploads/2014/08/terrarium_3.jpg" alt="terrarium_3" width="750" height="500" /></div></p> <p style="text-align: justify;"><div class="wp-caption"><img class="wp-image-1954 size-full alignnone" src="https://github.com/ankitdarda/ANKITDARDA.git/wp-content/uploads/2014/08/terrarium_4.jpg" alt="terrarium_4" width="750" height="500" /></div></p> <p style="text-align: justify;"><div class="wp-caption"><img class="size-large wp-image-1955 alignnone" src="https://github.com/ankitdarda/ANKITDARDA.git/wp-content/uploads/2014/08/terrarium_5.jpg" alt="terrarium_5" width="750" height="486" /></div></p> <p style="text-align: justify;"><div class="wp-caption"><img class="size-full wp-image-1958 alignnone" src="https://github.com/ankitdarda/ANKITDARDA.git/wp-content/uploads/2014/08/terrarium_8.jpg" alt="terrarium_8" width="750" height="500" /></div></p> <p style="text-align: justify;"><div class="wp-caption"><img class="size-large wp-image-1957 alignnone" src="https://github.com/ankitdarda/ANKITDARDA.git/wp-content/uploads/2014/08/terrarium_7.jpg" alt="terrarium_7" width="750" height="486" /></div></p> ]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Project Entry: World Architecture Community Award</title>
		<link>https://github.com/ankitdarda/ANKITDARDA.git/blog/world-architecture-community-award/</link>
		<pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2014 23:45:45 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ankitdarda]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Blog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[architecture]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[competition]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[scad]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://github.com/ankitdarda/ANKITDARDA.git/?p=1877</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[The World Architecture Community Awards is to highlight and publish remarkable projects that might otherwise remain unnoticed by the international public yet have the potential to inspire exciting questions about contemporary architectural discourse. Architects  from ALL countries can submit ALL of their buildings (realized or not) for the appreciation of the WA Community.  Member ratings will determine the 10 top-rated [&#8230;]]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p style="text-align: justify;"><span style="color: #666666;">The World Architecture Community Awards is to highlight and publish remarkable projects that might otherwise remain unnoticed by the international public yet have the potential to inspire exciting questions about contemporary architectural discourse. Architects  from ALL countries can submit ALL of their buildings <strong>(realized or not)</strong> for the appreciation of the WA Community. </span></p> <p style="text-align: justify;"><span id="more-1877"></span></p> <p><strong>Member ratings</strong> will determine the <strong>10 top-rated projects</strong> of the “Members’ Awards” and also help shaping the shortlist for the Final Assessment Panel. <strong>Votes of the Final Assessment Panel</strong> will specify <strong>20 projects</strong> from the shortlist following the aim of the awards.<strong>Honorary Members</strong> of the WA Community who may wish to take part in online voting will constitute the Final Assessment Panel.</p> <p>Please<strong> sign up with <span style="text-decoration: underline;"><a href="http://www.worldarchitecture.org/" target="_blank">WA Community</a> </span>and rate</strong>  or click on below entry images to open project page and increase the chances for getting recognized before <strong>29th August</strong>!</p> <p><div class="wp-caption"><a href="http://www.worldarchitecture.org/world-buildings/hzzch/upcycled-narrow-gauge-railways-heritage-park-building-page.html" target="_blank"><img class="alignleft wp-image-1818 size-thumbnail" src="https://github.com/ankitdarda/ANKITDARDA.git/wp-content/uploads/2014/06/featured_projects_railways-150x150.jpg" alt="featured_projects_railways" width="150" height="150" /></a></div> <div class="wp-caption"><a href="http://www.worldarchitecture.org/world-buildings/hzzcc/point-influenced-adaptive-revit-canopy-building-page.html" target="_blank"><img class="alignleft wp-image-1813 size-thumbnail" src="https://github.com/ankitdarda/ANKITDARDA.git/wp-content/uploads/2014/06/featured_projects_para1-150x150.jpg" alt="featured_projects_para1" width="150" height="150" /></a></div></p> <p><div class="wp-caption"><a href="http://www.worldarchitecture.org/world-buildings/hzzce/collective-housing-layered-density-building-page.html" target="_blank"><img class="alignleft wp-image-1807 size-thumbnail" src="https://github.com/ankitdarda/ANKITDARDA.git/wp-content/uploads/2014/06/featured_projects_foreclosure-150x150.jpg" alt="featured_projects_foreclosure" width="150" height="150" /></a></div> <div class="wp-caption"><a href="http://www.worldarchitecture.org/world-buildings/hzzcp/self-contained-revit-groundscraper-building-page.html" target="_blank"><img class="alignleft wp-image-1814 size-thumbnail" src="https://github.com/ankitdarda/ANKITDARDA.git/wp-content/uploads/2014/06/featured_projects_para2-150x150.jpg" alt="featured_projects_para2" width="150" height="150" /></a></div></p> ]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Upcycled: Railways Heritage Park &#124; My Museum 1+1 online contest</title>
		<link>https://github.com/ankitdarda/ANKITDARDA.git/blog/upcycled-railways-heritage-park/</link>
		<pubDate>Tue, 15 Jul 2014 18:49:37 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ankitdarda]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Blog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[architecture]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[installation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[young designer of the year]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://github.com/ankitdarda/ANKITDARDA.git/?p=1823</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[TELL A FAVORITE MUSEUM IN 1 IMAGE AND 1 PHRASE ONLINE CONTEST! After honored with Young Designer of the Year 2014 Special Mention Award, Railways Heritage Park is once again among Online Contestant for Museum Category. &#8220;Upcycled: Railways Heritage Park&#8220; is among the Inexhibit.com My-Museum &#124;1+1&#124; online entries and needs your voting support to win this exciting contest. Please Register at [&#8230;]]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p style="text-align: justify;">TELL A FAVORITE MUSEUM IN 1 IMAGE AND 1 PHRASE ONLINE CONTEST! After honored with Young Designer of the Year 2014 Special Mention Award, Railways Heritage Park is once again among Online Contestant for Museum Category.<em> &#8220;<strong><span style="text-decoration: underline; target: _blank;"><a href="http://www.inexhibit.com/design/upcycled-railways-heritage-park/" target="_blank">Upcycled: Railways Heritage Park</a></span></strong>&#8220;</em> is among the Inexhibit.com <a href="http://www.inexhibit.com/incontest/museum-11-online-contest/" target="_blank"><i style="font-weight: bold;">My-Museum |1+1| </i></a>online entries and needs your voting support to win this exciting contest. Please Register at <em><strong><a href="www.inexhibit.com" target="_blank">Inexhibit.com</a></strong></em> and vote until September 5.</p> <p style="text-align: justify;"><span id="more-1823"></span></p> <p style="text-align: justify;">Inexhibit.com has recently announced the online contest to promote permanent/temporary museums online across the world. The “perfect combination” of an image and a sentence capable together to depict the museum that you like most will win exciting prices. The <i style="font-weight: bold;"><a href="http://www.inexhibit.com/incontest/museum-11-online-contest/" target="_blank">My-Museum |1+1|</a> </i>is an online contest open to graphic designers, creative people, poets, writers, photographers, architects, designers, students, artists, art enthusiasts and passionate travellers.</p> <p style="text-align: justify;">Deadline for public voting: <strong>5 September 2014</strong> | <strong>No Entry Fee</strong> | The contest’s winner will receive a money prize of <strong>400,00 USD</strong>. The Top 10 proposals will receive also a <strong>Certificate of merit</strong>.</p> <p> Check out their <a href="http://loanigo.co.uk/small-loans/">Homepage</a> for more information.</p> <p>According to Bridge Payday, <a href="https://citrusnorth.com/bad-credit-loans-guaranteed-approval/">Financial mistakes happen anytime.</a> Learn more about how a bridge loan works, and what the benefits of a bridge loan are.</p> <p style="text-align: justify;">Thank you for your support!</p> <p style="text-align: justify;"> ]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Young Designer of the Year 2014</title>
		<link>https://github.com/ankitdarda/ANKITDARDA.git/blog/young-designer-of-the-year-2014/</link>
		<pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2014 22:32:34 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ankitdarda]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Blog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[installation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[urban]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Work-Sample]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[young designer of the year]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://github.com/ankitdarda/ANKITDARDA.git/?p=417</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[Recently, our executed project Railways Heritage park got special mention for the young designer of the year 2014 competition under urban design category organized by the leading architecture and design magazine&#160;Indian Architects and Builders at Mumbai followed by the 361 degrees conference and soon the project is going to publish in their upcoming architecture issue. [&#8230;]]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p style="text-align: justify;">Recently, our executed project <a title="Railway Heritage Park" href="https://github.com/ankitdarda/ANKITDARDA.git/gallery/railway-heritage-park/" target="_blank">Railways Heritage park</a> got special mention for the young designer of the year 2014 competition under urban design category organized by the leading architecture and design magazine&nbsp;<a href="https://www.facebook.com/indian.architect.and.builder" target="_blank">Indian Architects and Builders</a> at Mumbai followed by the 361 degrees conference and soon the project is going to publish in their upcoming architecture issue. The special mention entry can be seen <a title="special mention | railways heritage park" href="https://www.facebook.com/media/set/?set=a.497790153666826.1073741894.226753014103876&amp;type=1" target="_blank">here</a>.<span id="more-417"></span></p> <p style="text-align: justify;"><div class="wp-caption"><img class="ngg_displayed_gallery mceItem" style="line-height: 1.5em;" src="https://github.com/ankitdarda/ANKITDARDA.git/nextgen-attach_to_post/preview/id--442" alt=""></div></p> <p style="text-align: justify;">The park had been executed and inaugurated&nbsp;for the completion of 150 years of Narrow-Gauge Railways history in Vadodara region. Followed by the SAARC Railway Convention with different competition and exhibition from the local artists and enthusiasts.&nbsp;It was an collaborative accomplishment by the interdisciplinary professionals from varied design and non-design background like architects, landscape architect, industrial designers, engineers, museology&nbsp;and historical PhD students. Speaking of landscape architects, if you&#8217;re planning to renovate your backyard, visit <a href="http://brandonfosteroklahoma.com/about-brandon-foster/">brandon foster tulsa and owasso</a> website to read some of the best tips in landscaping. Visit this website <a href="https://www.adinfusion.com/branding-design/">https://www.adinfusion.com/branding-design/</a> and learn more. Railway Heritage Park is archetype of the successful adaptive reuse and recycling of the railways junk into a prosperous &nbsp;heritage platform for railway enthusiasts, passengers, local residents and region itself. Further detail can be reviewed <a title="Railway Heritage Park" href="https://github.com/ankitdarda/ANKITDARDA.git/gallery/railway-heritage-park/" target="_blank">here</a>.</p> ]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>SCAD Sand Art Festival Fund-Fun raising!!</title>
		<link>https://github.com/ankitdarda/ANKITDARDA.git/blog/scad-sand-art-festival-fund-fun-raising/</link>
		<comments>https://github.com/ankitdarda/ANKITDARDA.git/blog/scad-sand-art-festival-fund-fun-raising/#respond</comments>
		<pubDate>Sun, 29 Dec 2013 22:18:57 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ankitdarda]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Blog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[design]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[fabrication]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[installation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sand art festival]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[scad]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Work-Sample]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://github.com/ankitdarda/ANKITDARDA.git/?p=300</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[The fun-fund raising from last quarter fabrication and prototyping class with Prof. Bacha at SCAD Sand Art Festival, Wind Sculpture category.  A team effort fund raising for our so called final project! We used 2X2 inches squares of different matte and gloss photo film to showcase a photo booth like wind sculpture. The efforts can [&#8230;]]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p style="text-align: justify;">The fun-fund raising from last quarter fabrication and prototyping class with Prof. Bacha at <a title="Sand Art Festival" href="http://web.scad.edu/experience/events/sand-arts/2013/" target="_blank">SCAD Sand Art Festival</a>, Wind Sculpture category.  A team effort fund raising for our so called final project! We used 2X2 inches squares of different matte and gloss photo film to showcase a photo booth like wind sculpture. The efforts can be seen below in slideshow:<span id="more-300"></span></p> <p style="text-align: justify;"><div class="wp-caption"><img class="alignleft wp-image-2201" src="https://github.com/ankitdarda/ANKITDARDA.git/wp-content/uploads/2013/12/sand-art3.jpg" alt="sand-art3" width="750" height="804" /></div> <div class="wp-caption"><img class="alignleft wp-image-2202" src="https://github.com/ankitdarda/ANKITDARDA.git/wp-content/uploads/2013/12/sand-art4.jpg" alt="sand-art4" width="750" height="499" /></div> <div class="wp-caption"><img class="alignleft wp-image-2203" src="https://github.com/ankitdarda/ANKITDARDA.git/wp-content/uploads/2013/12/sand-art5.jpg" alt="sand-art5" width="750" height="1001" /></div> <div class="wp-caption"><img class="alignleft wp-image-2204" src="https://github.com/ankitdarda/ANKITDARDA.git/wp-content/uploads/2013/12/sand-art6.jpg" alt="sand-art6" width="750" height="1001" /></div> <div class="wp-caption"><img class="alignleft wp-image-2205" src="https://github.com/ankitdarda/ANKITDARDA.git/wp-content/uploads/2013/12/sand-art7.jpg" alt="sand-art7" width="750" height="1001" /></div> <div class="wp-caption"><img class="alignleft wp-image-2206" src="https://github.com/ankitdarda/ANKITDARDA.git/wp-content/uploads/2013/12/sand-art1.jpg" alt="sand-art1" width="750" height="499" /></div></p> <p style="text-align: justify;"><span style="line-height: 1.5em;">The adventurous event can be evident from the following photograph (via SCAD Sand art festival/other sources) and finally we occupied third place with $200 prize money for our wind sculpture category!! </span><span style="line-height: 1.5em;">It was an enthusiastic and my very first experience working with classmates, Tybee beach, and professor. The other fabrication and prototyping work from same class can be reviewed </span><a style="line-height: 1.5em;" title="Digital Fabrication &amp; Prototyping" href="https://github.com/ankitdarda/ANKITDARDA.git/gallery/digital-fabrication-prototyping/">HERE</a><span style="line-height: 1.5em;">.</span></p> ]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>https://github.com/ankitdarda/ANKITDARDA.git/blog/scad-sand-art-festival-fund-fun-raising/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>From architectonics to archi-(elec)-tronics!</title>
		<link>https://github.com/ankitdarda/ANKITDARDA.git/blog/architectonics/</link>
		<comments>https://github.com/ankitdarda/ANKITDARDA.git/blog/architectonics/#comments</comments>
		<pubDate>Sun, 29 Dec 2013 21:29:20 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ankitdarda]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Blog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bare conductives]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[installation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[tech]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Work-Sample]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://github.com/ankitdarda/ANKITDARDA.git/?p=314</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[Let the creativity interact with some electric shocks! With Bare Conductive paint you can make almost any surface to interact and end-up into electronic gadget with different creative approaches. Definitely next experiment is not far within buildings/installation architectonics. Great technology and material to enhance the user experience. Visit URL &#8211; WebDesign499 and learn more. I [&#8230;]]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p style="text-align: justify;">Let the creativity interact with some electric shocks! With Bare Conductive paint you can make almost any surface to interact and end-up into electronic gadget with different creative approaches. Definitely next experiment is not far within buildings/installation architectonics. Great technology and material to enhance the user experience. <a href="https://www.webdesign499.com/web-design-riviera-beach/">Visit URL &#8211; WebDesign499</a> and learn more. I had always imagined about this crazy things but now we can actually create and get engaged with all these innovations!</p> <p style="text-align: justify;"><span id="more-314"></span></p> <p style="text-align: justify;">About the Product: <a title="bareconductive.com" href="http://www.bareconductive.com/" target="_blank">Bare Conductive Ltd.</a> focuses on the development and manufacture of electrically conductive materials. In the fall of 2011, Bare launched its first product, Bare Paint. This is the first non-toxic conductive paint aimed at individuals interested in engaging with interactive electronics and in bringing surfaces to life. Bare&#8217;s products provide users with an exciting platform perfect for prototyping, experimenting, and learning about electronics.</p> <p style="text-align: justify;"><div class="wp-caption"><img class="ngg_displayed_gallery mceItem" src="https://github.com/ankitdarda/ANKITDARDA.git/nextgen-attach_to_post/preview/id--321" alt="" /></div></p> <p style="text-align: justify;">Electrically Conductive Paint for makers of all ages. Draw circuits on paper, or make surfaces interactive. Our pens and kits can get you started today!Taking the conductive paint out the hands of industry and to DIY enthusiasts, Bare Paint is available in both a jar and pen. You can find Bare Paint online or at RadioShack stores around the United States. The site offers classroom stationary kits, battery packs, light house models security services from <a href="https://469locksmith.com/areas/mckinney/">Mckinney locksmith services</a>, and tutorials to get the creative juices flowing. What could you make with Bare Paint? You can also find more architecture case studies and installations on the product website.</p> <p style="text-align: justify;">Via <a href="http://inhabitat.com/">inhabitat.com</a>,  <a title="bareconductive.com" href="http://www.bareconductive.com/" target="_blank">Bare Conductive Ltd.</a></p> ]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>https://github.com/ankitdarda/ANKITDARDA.git/blog/architectonics/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>2</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>Portfolio Mock Branding</title>
		<link>https://github.com/ankitdarda/ANKITDARDA.git/blog/portfolio-mock-branding/</link>
		<comments>https://github.com/ankitdarda/ANKITDARDA.git/blog/portfolio-mock-branding/#respond</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2013 22:29:47 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ankitdarda]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Blog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[branding]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[portfolio]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Work-Sample]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://github.com/ankitdarda/ANKITDARDA.git/?p=206</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[Sample mock branding images for my architecture portfolio 2014 Book with cover!  After six hours of stressful struggle with the Photoshop and internet, finally here is my portfolio mock branding sample ready for slide show. I always wanted to work and create on my own professional looking branding  mock. I used few free Photoshop templates [&#8230;]]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p style="text-align: justify;">Sample mock branding images for my architecture portfolio 2014 Book with cover!  After six hours of stressful struggle with the Photoshop and internet, finally here is my portfolio mock branding sample ready for slide show. I always wanted to work and create on my own professional looking branding  mock. I used few free Photoshop templates and actions from different websites for mock branding with my portfolio images. Template credit and copy right belong to respected website with content copyright belongs to myself.<span id="more-206"></span></p> <p style="text-align: justify;"><div class="wp-caption"><img class="ngg_displayed_gallery mceItem" src="https://github.com/ankitdarda/ANKITDARDA.git/nextgen-attach_to_post/preview/id--237" alt="" /></div></p> <p style="text-align: justify;">Please click on image to activate slide show. The entire mock branding for my design diagonal brand can be seen <a title="Product Branding" href="https://github.com/ankitdarda/ANKITDARDA.git/gallery/product-branding/">HERE</a>!</p> <p style="text-align: justify;">Keep calm and carry on good work!!</p> ]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>https://github.com/ankitdarda/ANKITDARDA.git/blog/portfolio-mock-branding/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>H&#038;M Storefront, Broughton Infill</title>
		<link>https://github.com/ankitdarda/ANKITDARDA.git/blog/hm-storefront-broughton-infill/</link>
		<comments>https://github.com/ankitdarda/ANKITDARDA.git/blog/hm-storefront-broughton-infill/#respond</comments>
		<pubDate>Sat, 14 Dec 2013 00:39:22 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ankitdarda]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Blog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cultural]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[H&M]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[historic]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[landscape]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[scad]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[urban]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Work-Sample]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://github.com/ankitdarda/ANKITDARDA.git/?p=149</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[Three weeks to finish quarter and another urban infill project. This time sponsored but not commissioned! I will hope to keep the same spirit and inspiration within myself. It might be good opportunity for city and street itself by welcoming the retail giant H&#38;M storefront .. Welcome to Broughton Street! But, Where am I going [&#8230;]]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p style="text-align: justify;">Three weeks to finish quarter and another urban infill project. This time sponsored but not commissioned! I will hope to keep the same spirit and inspiration within myself. It might be good opportunity for city and street itself by welcoming the retail giant H&amp;M storefront .. Welcome to Broughton Street! But, Where am I going and my opportunities? Am I expecting much from myself or is that something I desperately needed and should concentrate on? Whatever the reasons or circumstances, I need to move on with this too. Only brand can attract another and this time its H&amp;M with SCAD.<span id="more-149"></span></p> <p style="text-align: justify;"><div class="wp-caption"><a href="https://github.com/ankitdarda/ANKITDARDA.git/wp-content/uploads/2013/12/HM-logo_CMYK.png"><img class="alignleft size-medium wp-image-150" src="https://github.com/ankitdarda/ANKITDARDA.git/wp-content/uploads/2013/12/HM-logo_CMYK-300x192.png" alt="HM-logo_CMYK" width="300" height="192" /></a></div></p> <p style="text-align: justify;"> <p style="text-align: justify;"> <p style="text-align: justify;"> <p style="text-align: justify;"> <p style="text-align: justify;"> <p style="text-align: justify;">Lets do it! All iz well..All iz well..!</p> <p style="text-align: justify;">~</p> <p style="text-align: justify;">finally the gallery client review done and ready for second round next quarter with more exciting review by H&amp;M in-house designers. Hopefully the design will be able to crack that too.. The original design can be seen on the second part of this project page <a title="H&amp;M Urban Infill" href="https://github.com/ankitdarda/ANKITDARDA.git/gallery/hm-urban-infill/">HERE</a>.</p> ]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>https://github.com/ankitdarda/ANKITDARDA.git/blog/hm-storefront-broughton-infill/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>Chinese Brush Painting Workshop</title>
		<link>https://github.com/ankitdarda/ANKITDARDA.git/blog/chinese-brush-painting-workshop/</link>
		<comments>https://github.com/ankitdarda/ANKITDARDA.git/blog/chinese-brush-painting-workshop/#respond</comments>
		<pubDate>Sat, 14 Dec 2013 00:11:47 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ankitdarda]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Blog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[chinese brush painting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[scad]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[workshop]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://github.com/ankitdarda/ANKITDARDA.git/?p=142</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[Recently I got an opportunity through Prof. Josh Yu at SCAD MOA, to interact with my untouched part of Chinese brush painting. It was very informative and intellectual experience with colors, canvas as well the east/west painting technique. I wasn&#8217;t prepared for it but the enthusiasm and adventure took me a long way! This quarter [&#8230;]]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Recently I got an opportunity through Prof. Josh Yu at SCAD MOA, to interact with my untouched part of Chinese brush painting. It was very informative and intellectual experience with colors, canvas as well the east/west painting technique. I wasn&#8217;t prepared for it but the enthusiasm and adventure took me a long way! This quarter had came with me many surprises and this was not very different and what I was trying to learn to be myself in every situation.<span id="more-142"></span></p> <p><div class="wp-caption"><img class="alignleft size-medium wp-image-143" src="https://github.com/ankitdarda/ANKITDARDA.git/wp-content/uploads/2013/12/IMG_7596_01-300x199.jpg" alt="IMG_7596_01" width="300" height="199" /></div></p> <p>&nbsp;</p> <p>&nbsp;</p> <p>&nbsp;</p> <p>&nbsp;</p> <p>&nbsp;</p> <p>Thanks to Latoya for forwarding me information about this opportunity and photographs. She had made a very quick portrait, nicely done and signed by professor with traditional Chinese stamp. Amazing!</p> <p><div class="wp-caption"><img class="alignleft size-medium wp-image-144" src="https://github.com/ankitdarda/ANKITDARDA.git/wp-content/uploads/2013/12/IMG_7597_01-199x300.jpg" alt="IMG_7597_01" width="199" height="300" /></div></p> <p>&nbsp;</p> <p>&nbsp;</p> <p>&nbsp;</p> <p>&nbsp;</p> <p>&nbsp;</p> <p>&nbsp;</p> <p>&nbsp;</p> <p>And finally after very long struggle my first Chinese brush painting.</p> <p><div class="wp-caption"><img class="alignleft size-medium wp-image-145" src="https://github.com/ankitdarda/ANKITDARDA.git/wp-content/uploads/2013/12/IMG_7600_01-199x300.jpg" alt="IMG_7600_01" width="199" height="300" /></div></p> <p>&nbsp;</p> <p>&nbsp;</p> <p>&nbsp;</p> <p>&nbsp;</p> <p>&nbsp;</p> <p>&nbsp;</p> <p>&nbsp;</p> <p>Later night, I realized that it was very long time after I felt very relaxed and met someone again I used to be..</p> <p>&nbsp;</p> ]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>https://github.com/ankitdarda/ANKITDARDA.git/blog/chinese-brush-painting-workshop/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>Architectural Ceramics</title>
		<link>https://github.com/ankitdarda/ANKITDARDA.git/blog/architectural-ceramics/</link>
		<comments>https://github.com/ankitdarda/ANKITDARDA.git/blog/architectural-ceramics/#respond</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2013 12:34:06 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ankitdarda]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Blog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ceramics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[scad]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Work-Sample]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://github.com/ankitdarda/ANKITDARDA.git/?p=61</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[Congratulations! You got new spam mail! Late night when I was clearing my SCAD mailbox, realized that I got another unwanted spam after long time. It was mail from &#8216;SCAD Port City Review Literary Art Journal&#8217; confirmed that my work from &#8216;architectural ceramics&#8217; class will be featured in SCAD&#8217;s student work journal edition 2014. I [&#8230;]]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p style="text-align: justify;">Congratulations! You got new spam mail!</p> <p style="text-align: justify;">Late night when I was clearing my SCAD mailbox, realized that I got another unwanted spam after long time. It was mail from &#8216;SCAD Port City Review Literary Art Journal&#8217; confirmed that my work from &#8216;architectural ceramics&#8217; class will be featured in SCAD&#8217;s student work journal edition 2014. I am glad that I have made worth of my small experience with ceramics exploration. A gift and dedicated to my dearest Mother..<span id="more-61"></span></p> <p style="text-align: justify;"><div class="wp-caption"><img class="alignleft size-medium wp-image-136" src="https://github.com/ankitdarda/ANKITDARDA.git/wp-content/uploads/2013/12/bd11-189x300.jpg" alt="bd1" width="189" height="300" /></div></p> <p style="text-align: justify;"> <p style="text-align: justify;"> <p style="text-align: justify;"> <p style="text-align: justify;"> <p style="text-align: justify;"> <p style="text-align: justify;"> <p style="text-align: justify;"> <p style="text-align: justify;">Similar work samples can be view on <a title="Basic Design" href="https://github.com/ankitdarda/ANKITDARDA.git/gallery/basic-design/">Basic design</a> gallery section of website.</p> ]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>https://github.com/ankitdarda/ANKITDARDA.git/blog/architectural-ceramics/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
